So in the previous session we learn that we can
在之前部分 我们了解到
add to linear models to obtain a third model.
可以添加到线性模型中 得到第三个模型
As a matter of fact, we did even more.
实际上我们还可以做更多事情
We can take a linear combination of two models.
我们可以得到两个模型的线性组合
So, the first model times a constant plus the second model times a
第一个模型乘以一个常量加上第二个模型乘以
constant plus a bias and that gives us a non-linear model.
一个常量 再加上偏差 可以得到非线性模型
That looks a lot like perceptrons where we can take a value times a constant plus
这看起来很像是感知器 其中我们使用第一个值乘以一个常量
another value times a constant plus a bias and get a new value.
加上另一个值乘以一个常量 再加上偏差 得到一个新的值
And that's no coincidence.
这并不是巧合
That's actually the building block of Neural Networks.
实际上这是神经网络的基础
So, let's look at an example.
那么我们来观察一个例子
Let's say, we have this linear model where the linear equation is 5x1 minus 2x2 plus 8.
例如我们有这样的线性模型 其中线性方程式是 5x1 - 2x2 + 8
That's represented by this perceptron.
通过这个感知器表现出来
And we have another linear model with equations 7x1 minus
我们有另一个线性模型 方程式
3x2 minus 1 which is represented by this perceptron over here.
是 7x1 - 3x2 - 1
Let's draw them nicely in here and let's use another perceptron
我们可以在这里清晰地绘制出来 使用另一个感知器
to combine these two models using the Linear Equation,
利用线性方程把两个模型组合起来
seven times the first model plus five times the second model minus six.
7 乘以第一个模型加上 5 乘以第二个模型 减去 6
And now the magic happens when we join these together and we get a Neural Network.
当我们把两个合并在一起时 发生了神奇的事情 我们得到了神经网络
We clean it up a bit and we obtain this. All the weights are there.
我们稍加清洗后得到这个 所有的权重都在这里
The weights on the left,
左侧的权重
tell us what equations the linear models have.
告诉我们线性模型的方程式是什么
And the weights on the right,
而右侧的权重
tell us what the linear combination is of
告诉我们两个模型的线性组合
the two models to obtain the curve non-linear model in the right.
得到右侧的曲线非线性模型
So, whenever you see a Neural Network like the one on the left,
那么无论何时你看到左侧这样的神经网络
think of what could be the nonlinear boundary defined by the Neural Network.
就会想到什么是神经网络定义的非线性边界
Now, note that this was drawn using the notation that puts a bias inside the node.
现在注意这个是利用符号法绘制的 在节点内部增加了一个偏差
This can also be drawn using the notation that keeps the bias as a separate node.
这也可以利用符号法绘制 使偏差仍然是独立的节点
Here, what we do is, in every layer we have
这里我们所做的是 在每层中 我们
a bias unit coming from a node with a one on it.
通过节点及其上面的内容得到偏置单元
So for example, the minus eight on the top node
例如顶层节点上的 -8
becomes an edge labelled minus eight coming from the bias node.
成为来自偏差节点的边缘 标记为 -8
We can see that this Neural Network uses
我们发现这个神经网络使用
a Sigmoid Activation Function and the Perceptrons.
一个 Sigmoid 激活函数和感知器